VICTOR HUGO LOPES MOTA SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

victormota042@gmail.com
in linkedin.com/in/victor-lmota/
https://github.com/MrVictor42/
Brasília - DF, Brazil (Willing to
Relocate)

About me

am a software engineer graduated from the University of Brasilia, Brazil, I like to help my co-workers, I always try to have a good relationship with them and learn as much as I can. I interned for two years at the Federal Senate, and worked as a Junior Developer for a year and a half at Tata Consultancy Services. I am currently a Junior Developer at Sea Tecnologia

Hard-skills

- Java / Kotlin
- MySQL
- Angular / React
- SonarQube
- Nexus
- Python

• Git / GitHub / GitLab

Soft-skills

- People and interpersonal skills
- · Self-awareness and self-learning
- Time management
- Emotional intelligence

Work Experience

Junior Developer - Sea Tecnologia

February 2023 - Current

Implementation, and maintenance of the functionalities requested by the client. Perform pairing, functional code, meetings with managers and maintenance on legacy code;

The main technologies used were:

- Java, Liferay Framework, Gitlab
- Angular, React e Freemarker

Junior Developer - Tata Consultancy Services

March 2021 - July 2022

Feature development, plus maintenance of unit and integrated tests to prevent behaviors unexpected events in a production environment;

The main technologies used were:

- Java com Spring Boot, JSP, JSF, Maven, Kotlin, HTML, CSS e JS

Desenvolvedor Full Stack - Globalspex

December 2022 - August 2022

Website development through wordpress framework, along with php.

The main technologies used were:

- Wordpress, PhP.

Education

Software Engineering - UnB Language Exchange - Dublin Ireland August 2013 - March 2021 July 2022 - December 2022